<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="manualIntro">Welcome to Dynamic Navlog. This application is an electronic replacement for standard paper Navigation Log or Operational Flight Plan that is used for VFR
    navigation. It provides features related to Time, Distance and Fuel calculations. The app is not a GPS navigation software and it does not include GPS tracking (at least not yet).</string>

    <string name="manualText1">The application consists of 4 screens <i>Flight Display</i>, <i>Settings</i>, <i>Navigation log</i> and <i>Time Control</i>. Each screen has its own separate task
        that includes: determining flight plan, weather conditions and aircraft performance. A new flight plan is supposed to be defined in the below order.</string>

    <string name="manualSettings">1. Settings</string>

    <string name="manualText2">Fill few self-explanatory text fields to define the flight plan keeping in mind the rules. Each field is optional, but providing more information unlocks more of the
        app\'s features. If you will not enter any fields you can still use the app as a stopwatch by the buttons at Time Control page. The flight plan name is mandatory if you want to save the
        plan. The weather information is mandatory for the calculation of the navigation log. The fuel related fields are mandatory to calculate fuel consumption. All setting can be changed at any
        time before or during the flight. Each change must be applied with the button "Apply and Save"</string>

    <string name="manualText21">Distance/speed units</string>

    <string name="manualText3">Selected units apply to all features. For example when Nautical Miles are selected, every distance and speed will be considered to be as NM and
        KT. The units must be specified before entering any dimensions.</string>

    <string name="manualText22">Units conversion</string>

    <string name="manualText4">The units can be changed at any time. When changed, the application will convert all units at each route point along with the wind speed and TAS.</string>

    <string name="manualText41">Display Zulu times</string>

    <string name="manualText5">If selected the app will display UTC times with small "z" on <i>Flight Display</i> and in the <i>Navigation log</i>.</string>

    <string name="manualNavlog">2. Navigation log</string>

    <string name="manualText6">On this page enter all waypoints as you do on standard navigation log. To add a waypoint, click the round button. In a popup dialog enter required fields. The field
        <i>From</i> will be automatically filled if possible, but can be changed if necessary. Try to use short codes for the waypoints. If longer name is required use the <i>Remarks</i> field to
        describe details like frequency of VOR/DME, altitude change etc.</string>

    <string name="manualText71">Alternative routes</string>

    <string name="manualText7">You can plan alternative routes by using the "Active" checkbox. If you anticipate the possibility of changing the route during the flight, you
        can enter alternative waypoints and mark them as "not active". During the flight you can change the checkboxes of alternate waypoints and the app will recalculate time and fuel for selected
        route. Example: you want to fly from A to B but the is a possibility to fly through Z (depending on the weather or ATC clearance, etc). In that case you want to setup a route: from A to B,
        but also from A to Z and Z to B, making the last two as "not active". You can check the required fuel and time for all variations. During the flight you can change the plan by activating
        A-Z and Z-B and deactivate A-Z. Notice that only waypoints that are ahead can be edited. It is not possible to deactivate current or past waypoints.</string>

    <string name="manualText81">Editing flight plan</string>

    <string name="manualText8">You can edit and change position of each waypoint by dragging them in the list (long press item and drag&amp;drop). The navigation log will be recalculated after
        every
        change.</string>

    <string name="manualTimeControl">3. Time control</string>

    <string name="manualText9">When the flight plan is defined you can start the timer with corresponding buttons.</string>
</resources>